adparatus.com 2013-07-25

# Adparatus :: Privacy Policy

Revised 05/09/2008

Market Precision (the "Company") is committed to your privacy. This privacy policy is designed to explain how we collect and use information on both the Adparatus website and through the use of the Adparatus software (the "Software"), and to help show how user privacy is protected. **  
** The Web Site

We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information (PII) from the web site unless you voluntarily provide such information to us. For example, when using the web site, you may choose to send to us certain Personal Information about yourself in an email or by completing an online form.

We collect Non-Personal Information from visitors to this web site. Such Non-Personal Information includes an individual's IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, clickstream data, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, system information (such as your operating system, machine ID, registry values, MAC address, hardware, settings, installed software, preferences or configuration of your computer), non-personal information from online forms, general geographic location and other non-personally identifiable information data. Keep in mind that none of the Non-Personal Information we collect can be used to identify you personally.

We do not use "cookies" in connection with this Web site. Cookies are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer in connection with your viewing a web page for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web page or the servers of the party who placed the cookie on your computer. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Service, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. We do not use cookies to retrieve Personal Information from your computer.

The Software

By installing the Software you grant permission for the Company to collect certain information based on your browsing habits. This may include, for example, your computer's IP Address, which is associated with the computer's connection to the Internet, but does not identify any particular user. This information is used to periodically display advertisements. The Company will not use any collected information to identify you personally.

What You'll See

All ads delivered as a result of installing the Software are identifiable by the Adparatus name or logo and the name of the Partner Application with which Adparatus was installed. You may receive one or more sponsored icons on your desktop when the Software is installed. The icons are shortcuts to offers provided by one of our advertisers and they will only appear if you agree to receive such offers during the installation process.

The Software displays advertisements in the form of pop-up or pop-under windows. These ads display based on your browsing habits, although we cannot guarantee that all ads you receive will be contextual in nature. These ads are discernible by their branding; all ads are labeled with both the Adparatus name and the name of the Partner Software with which the Software was installed. The software can always be completely and easily removed at any time by using the Windows Add or Remove Programs function found within the Control Panel or by clicking on Uninstall in the Adparatus program group. However, you should be aware that removing the Software may disable the Partner Software with which Adparatus was installed.

What We Collect

When the Software installs, an anonymous User ID and Referral ID from the Partner Application are generated within the Windows registry to track the total number of active Software users and the number of downloads attributed to Software Partners. Cookies and Pixels (also known as Web Beacons) are stored within your Temporary Internet Files to control the frequency and timing of ad delivery, and to temporarily track your response to advertisers' offers. Neither Cookies nor Pixels collect or convey any "Personally Identifiable Information" (information that specifically identifies you, such as your name or email address).

When you browse the web the Software tracks the URLs visited, including the domain and associated keywords attached to the domain. This information is passed to our servers along with your IP Address to determine if we can provide you with a relevant advertisement. The software also collects and aggregates the websites you visit which result in Domain Not Found or 404 Error Messages. No Personally Identifiable or User ID Information is associated or stored with this data.

Treatment of Personal Information

We do not collect any Personal Information about you in connection with the delivery or use of the Software, and we do not require Personal Information from you before downloading or installing the Software. We may use aggregated, anonymous information to develop reports for our clients so that they can better understand trends in online consumer behavior and how those trends relate to their businesses. While complete URLs are collected and uploaded to our servers, steps are taken to strip away any information that identifies you personally before URLs are stored.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about the Software or our Company, you should first consult our website at http://www.Adparatus.com. This site includes links to company information and current policies. If you have further questions or concerns, please [Contact Us](http://www.adparatus.com/contactus.php) through our website or email [support@adparatus.com](mailto:support@adparatus.com).

Changes

The Company reserves the right to change the provisions of this privacy policy at any time. We will always post these changes along with the date of such changes on the privacy page of the website located at [http://www.adparatus.com/privacy.html](http://www.adparatus.com/privacy.php) so you can understand what information we collect and how we use it. Your use of the Software following the posting of such changes to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any such changes.
